DUMPLINGS
HAIR SALON
Mrs. Li ? Oh , you 're so beautiful .
They say your dumplings are the most expensive .
Of course ! Please come in .
You 've come at the right time .
The water is boiling , I 've been waiting for you .
Actually , I recognized you .
I often saw you on TV when I first came to Hong Kong .
You were the best !
I quit acting a long time ago .
Please , have a seat .
Guess how old I am .
Sit over here , please .
Here .
Just take a guess , Mrs. Li .
I suppose ...
You 're in your thirties at most .
I 'm much older than that . They call me Aunt Mei .
But you don 't have wrinkles .
And I have fair skin , too .
I 'm my own best advertisement .
Your skin is great . I 'm impressed .
My dumplings are worth it .
You get what you pay for .
Mrs. Li !
I 'm putting in more cabbage for you .
I know you dislike chives because of their strong flavor .
This cabbage is great .
I 'll cut it fine , squeeze it dry ,
and put more ginger in the filling , okay ?
- You decide . - Okay .
YUE MEI PAVILION
The Northerners always say ,
" Good health comes from a nap and good eats come from dumplings . "
Dumplings have existed in China for more than 1,400 years .
But the Southerners still say ,
" It 's just dough stuffed with meat . Nothing special ! "
I only use high-gluten flour
for texture and chewiness .
I knead it well ,
until it is like a peeled egg .
Smooth , translucent , and soft .
Got to keep the filling from leaking out .
So that the juicy flavor explodes in the mouth .
Here you go , Mrs. Li .
Eat while it 's warm .
Take your time .
Baby , behave .
I eat this often . It 's so nutritious .
Sometimes I put in soup ,
sometimes it 's minced and steamed with citrus peel .
But adding the dumplings taste the best .
And they made me famous .
Baby ...
It 's a shame to discard this .
Wash it then bury it in the soil .
The flowers will bloom especially well .
Let me tell you ,
all expensive cosmetics claim to contain precious stuff like ...
bird 's nest , ginseng , pearl powder , pollen , royal jelly , whatever .
Those are useless .
For women to rejuvenate ,
you must start from the inside for the best results !
Only my secret recipe can do this .
Mrs. Li .
While eating it , think of the results . Don 't think of what it is .
Let me sing you a song .
It 's a custom of mine
to sing a song from my youth after my customer eats .
Take it as entertainment . Let me sing for you .
Clean up the kitchen . There will be a fridge delivery tomorrow .
Bring me some soup the day after tomorrow .
Sir , may I go now to deliver Mrs. Li her soup ?
Mr. Li , you 've been staying in our hotel for months .
Don 't you want to leave ?
My house is still being renovated .
My dining set from Paris is still in the warehouse .
It 's too humid now and my decorator refuses to work .
I 'm fussy like him .
If things don 't feel good to the touch , I reject them .
Please behave , Mr. Li .
All right , let 's behave .
I 'll behave when I eat .
- You are naughty . - It isn 't breaking .
What is it ?
Goodies .
Oh , my ...
It looks disgusting .
- Try some ? - No , thanks .
Your soup , ma 'am .
What did she say to Mr. Li ?
Oh ... I don 't know .
RADIOLOGY
I went through so much to get these .
They 've stepped up the surveillance here .
Because some paparazzi have shown up .
Hong Kong media is so nosy ...
Don 't come to pick up for the next two weeks .
Even the locals can 't get ahold of this stuff .
We 'll see .
- This is for you . - Thanks .
- Did you recognize him ? - What ? Who ?
- Wang Shouyi . - Wang Shouyi ?
Why did you two break up ?
It was long ago .
He loathed the one-child policy .
But I was aborting over ten fetuses a day .
That was 3,000 a year , 30,000 in ten years .
He was afraid that I would have a cursed child
for all the deaths I caused .
- It was our national policy . - Indeed .
I was only serving the people !
Indeed ! Bye , then .
This way , ma 'am .
- Put it through . - Which one ?
- The lunchbox . - Okay .
Open it .
Ham and egg on rice ?
Yes , lunch for my kid .
Ham and egg , plain rice .
- You may go . - Thanks .
Thank you .
I didn 't lie to you , trust me !
Shut up !
Anna !
Believe me , I didn 't lie to you .
Stop following me !
Or I 'll beat you up !
I taped these long ago because I was so fond of you .
Enjoy !
Hello ?
Fung !
Yes ...
Is it raining in London ?
Your mom said that you have maxed out your credit card .
Who are you with ? A girl ? Girlfriend ?
You 're dating ! Does your mom know ?
Your mom said she still hasn 't seen your report card .
You did well to choose me as your sponsor .
I 'll call you later .
Okay . Bye !
Dating at 13 !
So it 's puppy love ! Your son ?
Do I look that old ?
You ever consider having children ?
We are unable to . I don 't know whose problem it is ...
Don 't worry , you 'll soon regain your youth
as well as the heart of your man .
Do you have more potent stuff for faster results ?
The best are those in the 5th or 6th month .
Have to extract it by breaking the water sac then slide it out .
It 's covered by a layer of creamy fat .
The colors are defined . You can even see the cranium .
Its tiny limbs would still be moving around .
In the first trimester ... only this small .
By the third trimester , the meat would be too tough .
The 5th month is perfect , kitten-like .
So cute and so nutritious .
Let me show you .
This is it ! 80 years old .
She ate exactly this and feels 18 years old again , check that out !
This is what I made the fillings with .
You 're still afraid ?
I was a doctor .
In China , only the best minds could study medicine .
My forte was surgery with no bleeding .
So you 've saved many lives .
You can say I cleansed them .
Face it , we all have different fates that we can 't escape .
We must treasure our time here and live the best we can .
Honey ?
I 'm at your favorite bakery .
Want some custard tarts ?
- I 'm working . - Really ?
I 'll be home late .
Remember your promise .
Of course , our 15th anniversary .
I 'll keep you company tomorrow .
Okay . Bye .
You were on a trip last week .
You promised to celebrate our anniversary together .
I 'm just going for a few days .
I want to go visit my nephew in London , too .
Sure , if you like .
And go shopping , too .
So many " zeroes " ?
You used to laugh a lot .
Now even a big fat check can 't make you happy .
Laughing doesn 't always mean happy . You 're not going with me .
I 'll be gone only four or five days .
And if it 's more than five days ?
I 'll write you another check as a fine .
Fines are only for making mistakes .
Whatever .
Hello ?
About that contract , if you don 't send it over soon ,
I 'm going to change my mind .
The cap is $ 950 million .
I can accept an average of $ 2,000 per square foot .
Work it out with my secretary . I 'll be out of town .
Bye .
It tastes bland this time . What 's in that crunchiness ?
It 's okay , they have hands and feet already , you know .
And ears , too !
Those were bones ?
Nah , their bones are not hard .
I 'll chop it finer next time .
Simmer it in broth next time , it 'll be less greasy .
Broth is good , it keeps all the juices .
Are you done ?
- This can 't go on . - Pardon ?
My skin is still flabby .
No ! It 's much better !
I need your most potent stuff .
Don 't worry . I 'll find it .
It 's time for me to sing .
Suit yourself , but I must go .
Bye , Mrs. Li .
This way .
Don 't worry , I 'll find it for you .
- Call me when you do . - Trust me !
Aunt Mei ?
- Who are you ? - A friend of Mrs. Kam .
Oh ! Come in , my dear !
Speak up ! Beg for help .
I can 't help you .
Then who else can ?
Mrs. Kam said you were a great doctor in China . I believe her .
It 's too risky .
Let me recommend a hospital in Shenzhen .
It 's quite good , and legal , too .
I know .
- But I can 't afford the fees . - Black market , then .
You are the black market !
Hey !
I 'm not .
Her feet are swollen .
She 's showing .
I thought she gained weight .
She 's five months along .
I would have scraped the uterus in the first trimester .
But now the fetus is big . If I force it out ,
its bones might puncture the uterus .
I can 't do it , it 's too risky .
Please help her , she 's only 15 !
I quit long ago . It 's illegal .
But she can 't keep the baby ! She 's too young to be a mother .
Say something ! Speak up ! Beg for help !
I must tell you this .
Her dad did this to her !
Please help her with the abortion . He is a monster !
If the baby is born ,
I don 't know what to call it , my stepchild or grandchild ?
Have mercy on us !
Quit your job today .
And you 'll take care of me ?
I can afford that , given you 're so slim and eat so little .
- No , I love to eat . - You love to laugh , too .
Wow ! Your home is so grand !
So ? It 's empty .
It 's a house , not a home .
My husband is probably with some young girl now .
Didn 't he notice your change ?
I can 't wait ! I need your best stuff now .
For youth and beauty .
We women are always busy fighting our age .
I used to laugh a lot when I was young .
I joined a TV station right after high school .
I became a big star doing a series .
Li was the sponsor of my show .
I was doing a stunt , and fell down accidentally .
He was there and he held me up .
So you married him ?
I was only 20 then . Every girl at that age dreams about a perfect marriage .
He was in his 30s , and he loved me .
I thought I would live happily ever after .
All men love 20-year-old chicks .
Men in their 30s love 20-year-old chicks .
So do men in their 40s , and 50s .
Even men in their 60s and 70s love 20-year-old chicks .
I can accept that ,
as long as he doesn 't flaunt it .
Men are all the same .
All they want is sex .
What 's so good about a 20-year-old bimbo ?
What about you ?
Worse .
I broke up with my first love .
Then I married an uneducated man .
A cook !
We mainlanders all wanted to come to Hong Kong back then .
We would do anything just to get a Hong Kong ID .
As for me ...
I struggled hard before I got my identity card .
But then , I also got divorced .
I don 't think you 'd dare get a divorce .
Women like you are everywhere .
You 're lucky that you 've found me .
Otherwise ...
In five years , you 'll be wife-number-two , in ten years , wife-number-three .
And in 15 years , you 'll be wife-number-four .
Unlike you , I 'm my own boss .
You may be rich , but I am free .
Mrs. Li !
- Thanks , Aunt Mei . - You 're welcome , bye .
Mrs. Li . Not yet .
These are things money can 't buy , just like love .
The potent stuff is rare .
All right . Bye .
What a creepy place ?
Relax ...
There .
Relax .
Just relax .
It 'll be over soon .
Girl , it 's almost done . It 's been 18 hours already .
Relax .
You must try to relax , dear .
Will she be all right ?
Of course .
Try to relax .
Your cervix has not fully dilated yet , you 're not even fully grown .
We women must protect ourselves !
Don 't let others take advantage of you again .
Take care of your daughter and don 't let this happen ever again .
Her water broke !
- It 's okay . - Don 't be nervous .
I swear it will be over in ten seconds .
Breathe deeply !
Work with me , okay ? Relax ... hold on !
Relax ! Cry if you want to !
It 's fully dilated ! Stay calm and on my count ...
Three , two , one !
The head is out ... wait !
Where are my tongs ?
Relax !
Try to relax .
Beautiful .
Don 't be sad , my dear .
There 's no more life in this baby .
So fresh .
My dear .
You 'll be fine .
It 's over .
It 's done , my dear .
I 'll help you to my couch , get some rest .
- Thanks . - Take her shoes .
Oh , goodness .
Let me sing for you .
My ... you 're heavy .
I can 't hold you much longer .
Help .
Want some snacks , Mrs. Li ?
I 'll do steamed dumplings this time .
Need some wine , too .
It 's a boy .
A boy ?
See that little thing ?
So beautiful , so rare .
Boys hardly get aborted in China , you know , only girls do .
I didn 't use any oxytocin , just a catheter .
Drugs make it inedible .
It will damage its nervous system .
It is also a first-born , the most nutritious thing in this world .
You saw the mother , she 's not a prostitute .
She 's still in high school ! Young and healthy .
Then get on with it . How will you prepare it today ?
This will make you feel brand new .
Hello ?
My husband broke his leg .
Now you need me , after you broke your leg .
Normally , you wouldn 't care where I am .
You smell nice ...
look nice , too .
You haven 't touched me in ages .
Thirsty ?
I 'll get you some water .
It 's so hot in the street .
And we must go to Mongkok next .
Darn , I forgot about that .
Two more trunks to move .
- Oh , no . - Big trunks , too .
What 's wrong ?
- What is it ? - What 's this ?
- It 's blood ! - You kidding me !
- Here 's a tissue . - Whose blood is this ?
Kate ? Are you all right ?
Kate ... What 's going on ?
Answer me , Kate !
Kate ? What 's going on with you ?
I don 't want to die .
Don 't leave me , Kate . Please don 't die .
It 's all my fault !
Hello ?
I think the price is reasonable .
I 've been busy lately . My secretary Emily will follow up .
You can rest assured . Bye !
Could be sheep placentas ,
or Reishi mushrooms , or perhaps Snow Lotus .
Nah , I say it 's a major facelift .
She 's done something .
Or eaten something .
Mrs. Li .
You look fabulous ! Absolutely radiant !
Talking behind my back ?
No ! Just praising your look .
I 'll catch up later .
You 're so late ...
Perhaps she found herself a guru , or better , " voodoo . "
What evil thoughts !
That 's scary ...
Mrs. Li , take it easy , join us !
- Bon appetit ! - Thanks .
The food smells kind of fishy .
- Is it the beef ? - The beef ?
It 's the fish , I think .
Really ?
I don 't think so .
There is a strange smell here .
Something wrong with the food ?
The fish is fine , though .
But it really stinks here ...
What can it be ?
It 's coming from that side .
I 've forgot something ! Excuse me .
She 's off again .
Where is she going ?
The smell is gone . It 's so strange .
Aunt Mei ?
What 's in that " potent stuff " ?
What did you feed me ?
The fetus was sick , wasn 't it ?
Now I smell bad all over !
Nonsense !
I 've been eating them for 20 years and I 'm fine .
If anything happens to me , I 'll hold you responsible !
I 'll sue you !
Go ahead then and tell people what you 've been eating .
Don 't be silly , Mrs. Li .
It smells because it works . Stop over-reacting .
Look in the mirror tomorrow and you 'll be grateful .
What do I do now ?
Late abortion is hard to come by .
It was a child of incest . One in a million , you know .
You mean a child of incest turns me into this ?
Incest makes it extra potent , I tell you .
Hey ! Mrs. Li , hurry !
Turn on the TV ! Channel 2 is rerunning your series !
Heard you have a crush on that baby face ?
- No ... - You sure ?
You 've said he looks like Alan Tam .
I never said so .
- At least he 's a prom king . - So ?
Even a deck of cards has four kings .
Just admit it , you like him !
- No ! - Really ?
Mrs. Li , are you crying ?
Don 't be sad , be strong .
Take a hot bath , sip some whiskey ,
get a good sleep and you 'll be fine .
Good night , Mrs. Li .
Coming ...
Aunt Mei ?
Yes .
Hi , Mr. Li .
You 're running an illegal business here .
No , this is just a dumpling shop .
But you advocate cannibalism .
Does it really work ?
Please take a seat .
I 'll prove it to you .
Sit here , please .
You should never consider cannibalism immoral in China .
It 's existed since the beginning of time .
Li 's Herbalist Handbook clearly stated that
human flesh and organs are admissible ingredients for medical recipes .
During famines , what did people do for survival ?
They traded and cooked each other 's children !
Know the chef named Yi Ya ?
When his Emperor became tired of gourmet food and fancied human flesh ,
Yi Ya butchered and served his son as a meal to the monarch .
Tales abound of caring sons and daughters
cutting off flesh for their parents ' medicines .
The novel classic ,
Water Margin depicted heroes who savored their enemies .
One even served buns with human flesh filling .
Japanese have definitely eaten many Chinese .
You think our country could have survived all these wars and famines
without consuming human flesh ?
What about out of pure hatred , sometimes we 'd say
" I 'll skin you and eat you alive " ?
Our national hero Yue Fei once wrote ,
" Pep up with a meal of the invaders ' flesh ,
" celebrate with a drink of the invaders ' blood . "
When two people are deeply in love ,
all they desire is to be inside each other .
Inside each other 's skin , inside each other 's guts .
You were 20 in 1960 ?
That makes you 64 now !
Age is just a number .
But you 're an old lady !
It 's my body that counts .
Feel it , harder .
Is my body young enough ?
You can be the same , staying young forever .
Staying young by eating my dumplings .
- Hello . - This is Mrs. Li .
Do you have any supply ?
Money is not a problem , I need supplies . Hello ?
Mr. Li , will you come back ?
Yes , to eat your flesh .
- That 's a promise . - See you .
See you soon .
I shall wait for you
Aunt Mei !
Aunt Mei , it 's me .
Dizzy ? And rashes ?
It 's just stress .
You 'll be fine after you move back to your renovated home .
I 'll prescribe you something to ease the itch , okay ?
Hotel living is not for you .
Nurse .
Yes , Dr. Wong .
Mrs. Li 's chauffeur will come pick up her medication .
For how long should I write a prescription ?
- Give her a week 's worth . - Okay .
Miss Zhao .
Mr. Li 's secretary called and asked
why you skipped your ultrasound yesterday .
So ? I 'm here now .
Here 's your report .
Call us if your morning sickness continues .
Thanks .
- Goodbye . - Bye .
DR. SIU TUNG MAN , JOSEPH Specialist in Obstetrics Gynecology
Excuse me ?
Aunt Mei .
You scared me .
I was rude .
But as a woman , you know what I was going through .
I really need your help .
I 've retired .
Money is not a problem .
Forget it , Mrs. Li ! What happened was a dream .
Stop . Mrs. Li , cut the crap .
I beg you , I really need your help !
I really do !
Hello ? Hey .
Mr. Li , I 'm fixing my hair now . I 've been waiting for your call .
I want to see you soon , too !
Okay , bye !
Don 't move !
Dispatch , we 've arrived at 2103 .
Victim is male , badly stabbed . We need an ambulance .
We have his wife under control .
Tell them to hurry .
Please tell the ambulance to hurry , the victim is still breathing . Over .
Hello ? Hello ?
What 's this ?
- Must you scream ? - So much stuff left .
My husband is back with me .
I won 't let go again .
Give up .
I 've expected it all along .
But you 're pregnant .
He wanted me to keep the baby , he wanted a son .
And if it 's a girl ?
Then I 'll charge less . A boy costs more .
You plan to give birth ?
I 'm five months along .
Only four more months to go .
I 'm young , I can spare the time .
The pay would be enough for me to live well for a while .
I want your baby .
Why ? Inheritance issues ?
I want your baby now .
Now ?
Abort it .
You can be free again , and I can rest assured .
I 'll double whatever he pays you , how about that ?
Doctor , she 's in her second trimester . Do not induce a miscarriage .
Do not use any drugs either .
I don 't want the fetus dead before it comes out .
Use only a catheter and prostaglandin
to stimulate the contraction .
I want the fetus to be pure and wholesome .
This method will take a long time .
It will cause the mother a lot of pain .
What 's the big deal ? The pain will end .
You want to ...
keep the fetus ?
Yes , in its pure form .
What for ?
To make a specimen , a trophy .
The world 's most expensive trophy .
Hurry , then .
Leave the blinds open , I want to watch .
HUNG TAT MOTEL
Your first wish ?
A man to love me all my life .
And the second ?
Happiness always .
- The third ? - Hurry .
Youth and beauty .
- Of course , beauty . - Hurry , we should move !
Your wish of marriage is granted .
Go greet my guests first .
- I left something . - Hurry , then .
Subtitle translated by